B1.
David is listening to a radio program about Ni Ha Sheng, a great Chinese astronaut.
Listen to Nia's story and complete David's notes below.
In 1964, Nia Haisheng was born into a poor family in Hubei Province.
Life was hard for Nia.
His father died when he was only 16.
He had to do some part-time jobs during summer and winter holidays to earn money for school, but he had a strong interest in learning and was hard-working all the time.
At both primary and middle went to university.
There, he worked hard to learn about space travel and passed a test for PLA Air Force pilots.
In 1998, he became one of the first astronauts in China.
From 2005 to 2021, he travelled to space three times.
Nia Haisheng's story shows that non-stop learning and hard work are the key to success.